<div>
	<release project="RECOIL" version="3.4.0" date="2016-02-02">
		<ul>
			<li>Decoding the exact width of several formats, no more right-padding.</li>
			<li>Fixed crashes on invalid files.</li>
			<li>Faster calculation of unique colors.</li>
			<li>Honoring the aspect ratio of IFF and IMG.</li>
			<li>Fixed decoding of some Spectrum 512 SPC.</li>
			<li>Fixed downscaling artifacts in RECOILWin.</li>
		</ul>
		<ul title="IFF improvements">
			<li>Added decoding of multi-palette.</li>
			<li>Added decoding of RGB8 and RGBN.</li>
			<li>Ignoring the compression field of ACBM.</li>
			<li>Improved EHB and HAM detection.</li>
			<li>Improved contrast for 12-bit CMAP.</li>
		</ul>
		<ul title="New formats">
			<li>Apple IIGS: SH3.</li>
			<li>Atari 8-bit: Envision (MAP), EnvisionPC (MAP), KFX, Texture Editor (TXE), Interlace Logo Designer (ILD).</li>
			<li>Atari ST: NEOchrome Master (NEO, NEO+RST).</li>
			<li>Atari Falcon: XGA, Prism Paint (PNT, TPI).</li>
			<li>Commodore 128: VBM.</li>
		</ul>
		<ul title="Android changes">
			<li>Favorite files and folders and a shortcut to the downloads.</li>
			<li>Additional "back" on the action bar.</li>
			<li>Compatibility with old Androids.</li>
			<li>Full-screen error messages.</li>
		</ul>
	</release>

	<release project="RECOIL" version="3.3.0" date="2015-08-07">
		<ul>
			<li>Added support for multi-file pictures (extensions listed below with a plus sign).</li>
			<li>Added more variants of ICE and MAC formats.</li>
			<li>The LUM format contains 119 lines and not only 96.</li>
			<li>Fixed crash saving a PNG on Windows.</li>
			<li>Fixed Atari ST/STE formats unavailable on OS X.</li>
			<li>On Android, files are now sorted case-insensitively.</li>
		</ul>
		<ul title="New formats">
			<li>Amstrad CPC: SCR+PAL, WIN+PAL.</li>
			<li>Apple II: SPR.</li>
			<li>Atari 8-bit: CPI, CUT, KPR, LDM, LUM+COL, RAP, TXS.</li>
			<li>Commodore 64: KLA.</li>
			<li>MSX: SC5/GE5, SC7/GE7, SR5+PL5, SR7+PL7, YJK.</li>
			<li>Oric: CHS, HIR/HRS.</li>
			<li>Timex 2048: MLT.</li>
			<li>TRS-80: HR.</li>
			<li>TRS-80 Color Computer: CLP, GRF/MAX/P41/PIX, P11.</li>
		</ul>
	</release>

	<release project="RECOIL" version="3.2.0" date="2015-01-28">
		<ul title="New formats">
			<li>Amiga: INFO</li>
			<li>Amstrad CPC: SCR, HGB, FNT</li>
			<li>Apple II: HGR, DHR, SHR</li>
			<li>Atari 8-bit: RYS, HCI, MCPP</li>
			<li>Atari ST/STE: DUO/DU1, DU2, PL4</li>
			<li>BBC Micro: BB0, BB1, BB2, BB4, BB5, BBG</li>
			<li>Commodore 16: P4I</li>
			<li>Commodore 64: A64/WIG</li>
			<li>MSX: SCA, SCC, SRS</li>
			<li>PC: EPA, MSP</li>
			<li>ZX81: P</li>
		</ul>
	</release>

	<release project="RECOIL" version="3.1.0" date="2014-06-25">
		<ul title="New formats">
			<li>Commodore 64: GoDot (4BT), VIC, FLI Designer (FD2), Multi-Lace Editor (MLE)</li>
			<li>ZX Spectrum: 3</li>
			<li>Macintosh 128K: MacPaint (MAC)</li>
			<li>MSX: SC2, GRP, SC8, Graph Saurus (SR8)</li>
			<li>SAM Coupe: SCS4</li>
		</ul>
		<ul title="New ports">
			<li>OS X Quick Look plugin.</li>
			<li>GNOME 3 thumbnailer.</li>
			<li>Linux DEB and RPM binary packages.</li>
		</ul>
		<ul title="Android changes">
			<li>Search filenames using on-screen keyboard.</li>
			<li>Added file information and About boxes.</li>
			<li>Don't reset the gallery on orientation change.</li>
		</ul>
		<ul title="Other changes">
			<li>Disable per-line background color in the Funpaint (FUN) format.</li>
			<li>Reset RECOILWin zoom after a large image is open.</li>
		</ul>
	</release>

	<release project="RECOIL" version="3.0.0" date="2014-02-26">
		<p>RECOIL is a continuation of the First Atari Image Library (FAIL) project.
		In addition to the Atari 8-bit/Portfolio/ST/Falcon formats, RECOIL decodes
		Amiga, Commodore 64 and ZX Spectrum files.</p>
		<ul title="Other changes from FAIL 2.0.2">
			<li>New ports: Android, Paint.NET plugin.</li>
			<li>New Atari 8-bit formats: BGP, DGI, LEO, LUM, SIF.</li>
			<li>The default Atari 8-bit palette is now Altirra's PAL.</li>
			<li>The XnView plugin is now a single file and requires XnView 2.11 or newer.</li>
		</ul>
	</release>

	<release project="FAIL" version="2.0.2" date="2013-09-15">
		<p>New formats: Interlace Character Editor font (ICE), GEM Bit Image (IMG),
		Multi Palette Picture (MPP).</p>
		<p>This is the last release of FAIL. But don't worry! We are just renaming our project
		to Retro Computer Image Library (RECOIL), because we are going to support formats
		from 8-bit and 16-bit machines other than Atari. Stay tuned!</p>
	</release>

	<release project="FAIL" version="2.0.1" date="2013-04-24">
		<ul>
			<li>Added Atari 8-bit formats: IP2, IMN, ICN, DIN, IRG, IR2, VZI.</li>
			<li>Added "DEGAS Elite" icon (ICN).</li>
			<li>Fixed decoding of IPC.</li>
			<li>Thumbnail provider implemented for Windows 2000/XP.</li>
			<li>Fullscreen mode in HTML 5.</li>
		</ul>
	</release>

	<release project="FAIL" version="2.0.0" date="2013-02-15">
		<ul>
			<li>Library rewritten from C to the <a href="http://cito.sourceforge.net/">Ć programming language</a>.
			This made it possible to create the HTML 5 port.</li>
			<li>The rewrite included code clean-up and bug fixes in decoding of
			RIP, TIP, SGE, HR2, AGP, AP3/APV/DGP/ESC/ILC/PZM, APP, CIN, CCI.</li>
			<li>Added new formats: ICE PCIN (IPC), Daisy-Dot font (NLQ), PMG Designer (PMD),
			AtariTools-800 font (ACS), PhotoChrome (PCS), HPM, MCS, Anime 4ever (A4R),
			DuneGraph compressed (DGC, DC1), Canvas compressed (CPT), Interchange File Format (IFF),
			DEGAS Elite block (BL1, BL2, BL3), DEGAS Elite brush (BRU).</li>
			<li>Added auto-detection of Atari STE 4096-color palette.</li>
			<li>FAILWin and XnView show the computer family of the file format.</li>
			<li>FAILWin shows the number of alternating frames.</li>
			<li>The win64 package is now sufficient on 64-bit Windows, there's no need to install the win32 package.</li>
			<li>Reduced CPU and memory usage in fail2png.</li>
		</ul>
	</release>

	<release project="FAIL" version="1.4.0" date="2012-11-28">
		<ul>
			<li>Added Atari Falcon formats: Fuckpaint (PI4, PI9), DuneGraph (DGU, DG1),
			EggPaint (TRP), IndyPaint (TRU), GodPaint (GOD), Falcon True Color (FTC),
			DelmPaint (DEL, DPH).</li>
			<li>Added Atari ST formats: Spectrum 512 Smooshed (SPS), DeskPic (GFB),
			416x560 DEGAS (PI1).</li>
			<li>Created plugin for Imagine (might be interesting for Total Commander users,
			as Imagine includes a Total Commander plugin).</li>
			<li>Reduced CPU and memory usage in Windows thumbnail provider, ImageMagick
			and XnView.</li>
		</ul>
	</release>

	<release project="FAIL" version="1.3.0" date="2012-07-23">
		<ul>
			<li>Added Atari ST formats: DEGAS (PI1, PI2, PI3), DEGAS Elite (PC1, PC2, PC3),
			NEOchrome (NEO), Spectrum 512 (SPU, SPC), Tiny Stuff (TNY, TN1, TN2, TN3),
			STAD (PAC), CrackArt (CA1, CA2, CA3), Doodle (DOO), Art Director (ART).</li>
			<li>Added Atari Portfolio formats (PGF, PGC).</li>
			<li>More Atari 8-bit formats: Atari Player Editor (APL), Artist (ART),
			Ascii-Art Editor (ART), Atari CAD (DRG),
			AtariTools-800 (AGP, PLA, MIS, 4PL, 4MI, 4PM), ING 15 (ING),
			Lepix dialect of CIN, raw images (GR7, G10, G11).</li>
			<li>Fixed non-interlaced RIP modes.</li>
			<li>FAILWin extended with "First/Last file in directory", "Skip files on error".</li>
			<li>Narrow pictures were cropped in FAILWin.</li>
		</ul>
	</release>

	<release project="FAIL" version="1.2.0" date="2011-12-16">
		<ul>
			<li>Added decoding of ColorViewSquash (RGB), Blazing Paddles (CHR, SHP, WND),
			Magic Painter (MGP), Mad Designer (MBG), AtariGraphics (MIC),
			Fun with Art (FWA), Rambrandt (RM0, RM1, RM2, RM3, RM4), XL-Paint (XLP),
			XL-Paint MAX (MAX), SHIMC (SHC), Graph (ALL), APP View (APP),
			Semi-Graphic logos Editor (SGE), Dir Logo Maker (DLM), Movie Maker (BKG, SHP),
			BG9, G09, The Graphics Magician Picture Painter (SPC).</li>
			<li>Improved decoding of all RAW and MIC, some RIP and FNT files.</li>
			<li>Added the APV extension for the AP3 format.</li>
			<li>Created GNOME thumbnailer (for Linux file browser Nautilus).</li>
			<li>You may drag&amp;drop files to the FAILWin window.</li>
			<li>GR8 wasn't registered in ImageMagick.</li>
		</ul>
	</release>

	<release project="FAIL" version="1.1.0" date="2011-04-18">
		<ul>
			<li>Fixed decoding of ILC, AP3, RIP, PIC, CPR, HIP and CIN.</li>
			<li>Added support for MCH, IGE, 256, AP2, JGP, DGP, ESC, PZM, IST and RAW.</li>
			<li>Created Windows thumbnail provider.</li>
			<li>Fixed user interface issues in FAILWin.</li>
			<li>Fixed compilation errors with the new libpng.</li>
			<li>Updated installation for new ImageMagick.</li>
			<li>Moved source code from SVN to Git.</li>
		</ul>
	</release>

	<release project="FAIL" version="1.0.1" date="2010-08-25">
		<ul>
			<li>Created Windows setup.</li>
			<li>Created a coder for ImageMagick.</li>
			<li>Added MCP, GHG and HR2 formats.</li>
			<li>Improved the build process.</li>
		</ul>
	</release>

	<release project="FAIL" version="1.0.0" date="2009-08-25">
		<p>Initial release.</p>
	</release>
</div>
